<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[makedox]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>makedox</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 11:46:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 11:46:30 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[license]]></title><description><![CDATA[MIT LicenseCopyright (c) 2025 neuxdotdevPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.]]></description><link>license.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">docs/gh/neuxdotdev/license.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:58:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/twemoji/14.0.2/svg/1f4f0.svg" length="0" type="image/svg+xml"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/twemoji/14.0.2/svg/1f4f0.svg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[readme]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/neuxdotdev/neuxdotdev" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/neuxdotdev/neuxdotdev" target="_self"><code></code></a>NeuxDotDev is a personal account focused on developing open-source tools and projects that are useful for both beginners and advanced users.Our main goal is to create accessible technology solutions that help solve real problems and support learning and personal development.Providing simple, practical, and relevant tools to support a variety of user needs.Money is important, but helping others and providing real benefits is our top priority.
Open-source projects that are easy to learn and use
Practical tools for everyday and professional needs
Ideas, experiments, and contributions to the developer community
We are open to collaboration. Please submit issues, pull requests, or discuss them through this repository.<br>For questions or ideas, please contact us via <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/neuxdotdev/neuxdotdev/issues" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/neuxdotdev/neuxdotdev/issues" target="_self">GitHub Issues</a>.]]></description><link>readme.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">docs/gh/neuxdotdev/readme.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:54:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>